("Taps" ends)
(Howard:)Great.
(Sheldon:)Now I'm gonna have that song
in my head all day.
Look, I'm-I'm sorry
(Amy:)for your loss, but I think
(Amy:)I have something
that might make you feel better.
I got you a new computer!
(Sheldon:)How could you do that?
(Amy:)Do what?
(Sheldon:)Choosing a new laptop is
an incredibly personal ritual.
(Sheldon:)You have taken away
(Sheldon:)weeks of agonizing thought,
tedious research,
(Sheldon:)sleepless nights filled
with indecision. I j...
(Sheldon:)Haven't I lost enough today?
(Amy:)Well, the guy at the store said
this one is great.
Oh! Oh, the guy!
(Sheldon:)Oh, pardon me.
I-I didn't realize
you'd spoken to the guy.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, tell me,
(Sheldon:)did the guy choose one
with a 4K display
(Sheldon:)and a Thunderbolt port?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
Yeah?
D-Did the guy make sure
that this has a one-terabyte
solid-state drive?